<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>kbligue &#8211; Kim Dianne Ligue</title>
	<atom:link href="https://dianneligue.github.io/acadportfolio/author/kbligue/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://dianneligue.github.io/acadportfolio/</link>
	<description>Kim Dianne Ligue&#039;s online academic portfolio</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 12:10:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.0.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Hello world!</title>
		<link>https://dianneligue.github.io/acadportfolio/hello-world/</link>
					<comments>https://dianneligue.github.io/acadportfolio/hello-world/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[kbligue]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 12:10:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://dianneligue.github.io/acadportfolio/?p=1</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Welcome to WordPress. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start writing!]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Welcome to WordPress. This is your first post. Edit or delete it, then start writing!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://dianneligue.github.io/acadportfolio/hello-world/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Moody Flora</title>
		<link>https://dianneligue.github.io/acadportfolio/transforming-into-the-digital-enterprise/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[kbligue]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 04:37:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Organization]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://dianneligue.github.io/acadportfolio/transforming-into-the-digital-enterprise/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Surrounded by picturesque waterfalls, colorful florals, and their love for one another, Garry and Romeo’s Moc Chau elopement was both stunning and magical. So without wasting any more time, let’s [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Surrounded by picturesque waterfalls, colorful florals, and their love for one another, Garry and Romeo’s Moc Chau elopement was both stunning and magical.</p>



<p>So without wasting any more time, let’s get on to it. First up: Let’s look at some of the most crucial aspects or features that are required in every travel company website.</p>



<h4 id="enabling-online-travel-booking-and-reservations">Enabling Online Travel Booking and Reservations</h4>



<p>Before you can win over any visitor or potential customer, you must make a great first impression as a company. Your story about WHY and HOW your company came into existence is one of the most important things you can communicate to your audience.</p>



<p>If your visitors like you as a company, they are more likely to purchase services from you. So, your company’s story is crucial to be communicated in the right way and in the most beautiful manner possible.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p><em>The needs of a small-time tour operator are a lot different from the needs of a large international travel agency itself.</em></p><cite><strong>Steve Doe –&nbsp;</strong>Partner</cite></blockquote>



<hr class="wp-block-separator"/>



<p>Eventually, you must also offer them attractive and competitive tour packages. You must be able to clearly communicate to your customers what your services are, how they are different from others compelling manner.</p>



<p>Of course, you would want your visitors to conveniently reach out to you and contact you. You would want to display all the crucial information about your company, including a map that would show your visitors where exactly they will find you.</p>



<h5 id="displaying-company-information">Displaying Company Information</h5>



<p>Here are the major fear of rejection symptoms identified by psychologists:</p>



<ul><li>It’s all the better if you can accept payments online so that you can close the sales then and there.</li><li>It is much easier and convenient for your customers as well, and you too increase your chance of generating leads.</li><li>To make sure that your travel company website is compatible with some kind of online payment mechanism.</li><li>These will be crucial and highly beneficial for you later in the process.</li></ul>



<h1 id="h1-reject-the-fulfilling-prophecy">H1: Reject the Fulfilling Prophecy</h1>



<p>This is my average total monthly spending from one year living in Seattle’s Capitol Hill, one year living in San Francisco’s Upper Haight, one year traveling to 20 countries, and one month at a hotel in Bali. It is much cheaper for me to travel. Since the majority of my costs are from trains and flights, it’s significantly cheaper if I stay in one place.</p>



<h2 id="h2-focus-on-how-you-want-to-be">H2:Focus On How You Want to Be</h2>



<p>This is my average total monthly spending from one year living in Seattle’s Capitol Hill, one year living in San Francisco’s Upper Haight, one year traveling to 20 countries, and one month at a hotel in Bali. It is much cheaper for me to travel. Since the majority of my costs are from trains and flights.</p>



<h3 id="h3-construct-a-narrative">H3: Construct a Narrative</h3>



<p>Instead of working during the daylight hours and pushing all my free time to the worst part of the day, I prefer to enjoy the days and work at night. I get out of bed faster when I’m excited to go out, and when I don’t have to commute there’s just more time in the day. I like to work 7 days a week with flexible hours so I can take a day off when I please or enjoy an empty movie theater at 2pm.</p>



<h4 id="h4-tap-into-your-imagination">H4: Tap Into Your Imagination</h4>



<p>I now have friends all over the world whose life experiences are very different than mine and bring fresh perspectives to my ideas. I’m learning about the real problems that affect the world on a global scale, which will make me.</p>



<h5 id="h5-embrace-not-knowing">H5: Embrace Not Knowing</h5>



<p>There’s a growing community of “digital nomads” who live a location independent lifestyle. We’re software developers, designers, writers, journalists, engineers, and all sorts of people who share a passion for the work we do.</p>



<h6 id="h6-remember-you-will-survive">H6: Remember You Will Survive</h6>



<p>Three years ago I was preparing to leave my job at Microsoft to move to San Francisco to start a startup. My friend asked me “but why do you need to be in San Francisco when you can work on a computer from anywhere?” His question made a lot of sense. As I thought about it more, I began to question my assumptions about a “normal life” which don’t make sense in our modern world.</p>



<h1 id="h1-heading-1">H1: Heading 1</h1>



<h2 id="h2-heading-2">H2: Heading 2</h2>



<h3 id="h3-heading-3">H3: Heading 3</h3>



<h4 id="h4-heading-4">H4: Heading 4</h4>



<h5 id="h5-heading-5">H5: Heading 5</h5>



<h6 id="h6-heading-6">H6: Heading 6</h6>



<p>Three years ago I was preparing to leave my job at Microsoft to move to San Francisco to start a startup. My friend asked me “but why do you need to be in San Francisco when you can work on a computer from anywhere?” His question made a lot of sense. As I thought about it more, I began to question my assumptions about a “normal life” which don’t make sense in our modern world.</p>



<h5 id="displaying-company-information">Displaying Company Information</h5>



<p>Here are the major fear of rejection symptoms identified by psychologists:</p>



<ul><li>It’s all the better if you can accept payments online so that you can close the sales then and there.</li><li>It is much easier and convenient for your customers as well, and you too increase your chance of generating leads.</li><li>To make sure that your travel company website is compatible with some kind of online payment mechanism.</li><li>These will be crucial and highly beneficial for you later in the process.</li></ul>



<p>Three years ago I was preparing to leave my job at Microsoft to move to San Francisco to start a startup. My friend asked me “but why do you need to be in San Francisco when you can work on a computer from anywhere?” His question made a lot of sense. As I thought about it more, I began to question my assumptions about a “normal life” which don’t make sense in our modern world.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table><thead><tr><th><strong>Name</strong></th><th>Position</th><th>Office</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td>Erica Romaguera</td><td>Coach</td><td>Audi</td></tr><tr><td>Caleigh Jerde</td><td>Lawyer</td><td>Pizza Hut</td></tr><tr><td>Lucas Schultz</td><td>Librarian</td><td>Burberry</td></tr><tr><td>Carole Marvin</td><td>Educator</td><td>Starbucks</td></tr><tr><td>Woodrow Nikolaus</td><td>Massage Therapist</td><td>Jack Daniel’s</td></tr></tbody></table></figure>



<p></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tribal Rituals</title>
		<link>https://dianneligue.github.io/acadportfolio/how-bidens-victory-will-affect-the-trade-globally/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[kbligue]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 04:35:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Organization]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://dianneligue.github.io/acadportfolio/how-bidens-victory-will-affect-the-trade-globally/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The younger generation is a tech-savvy one, able to study, research, and apply online investing tools and techniques. Online&#160;provides countless opportunities for both fundamental, as do chat rooms and financial [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The younger generation is a tech-savvy one, able to study, research, and apply online investing tools and techniques. Online&nbsp;provides countless opportunities for both fundamental, as do chat rooms and financial and educational websites.&nbsp;</p>



<h2 id="mntl-sc-block_1-0-7">Take on More Risk</h2>



<p id="mntl-sc-block_1-0-8">An investor&#8217;s age influences the amount of risk they can withstand. Young people, with years of earning ahead of them, can afford to take on more risk in their investment activities. While individuals reaching retirement years may gravitate towards low-risk or risk-free investments\</p>



<h2 id="mntl-sc-block_1-0-10">Learn by Doing</h2>



<p id="mntl-sc-block_1-0-11">Young investors have the flexibility and time to study investing and learn from their successes and failures. Since investing has a fairly lengthy learning curve, young adults are at an advantage because they have years to study the markets and refine their investing strategies.</p>



<h2 id="mntl-sc-block_1-0-19">The Bottom Line</h2>



<p id="mntl-sc-block_1-0-20">Saving for retirement is not the only reason to make well-planned investments. Many investments, such as those made in dividend stocks, can provide an income stream throughout the life of the investment. Twenty-somethings have some definitive advantages over those who wait to begin investing, including time, the ability to weather increased risk, and opportunities to increase future wages. Even if you have to start small, it&#8217;s in your advantage to start early!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Bizzare Architect</title>
		<link>https://dianneligue.github.io/acadportfolio/when-you-should-hire-an-accountant-for-your-business/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[kbligue]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 04:33:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Enterprise]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Organization]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://dianneligue.github.io/acadportfolio/when-you-should-hire-an-accountant-for-your-business/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[An&#160;accountant&#160;is a practitioner of accounting or accountancy. Accountants who have demonstrated competency through their professional associations&#8217; certification exams are certified to use titles such as&#160;Chartered Accountant,&#160;Chartered Certified Accountant&#160;or&#160;Certified Public Accountant, [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>An&nbsp;<strong>accountant</strong>&nbsp;is a practitioner of accounting or accountancy. Accountants who have demonstrated competency through their professional associations&#8217; certification exams are certified to use titles such as&nbsp;Chartered Accountant,&nbsp;Chartered Certified Accountant&nbsp;or&nbsp;Certified Public Accountant, or Registered Public Accountant. Such professionals are granted certain responsibilities by statute, such as the ability to certify an organization&#8217;s&nbsp;financial statements, and may be held liable for professional misconduct. Non-qualified accountants may be employed by a qualified accountant or may work independently without statutory privileges and obligations.</p>



<p>Cahan &amp; Sun (2015)&nbsp;used archival study to find out that accountants’ personal characteristics may exert a very significant impact during the audit process and further influence audit fees and audit quality. Practitioners have been portrayed in popular culture by the stereotype of the humorless, introspective bean-counter.&nbsp;It has been suggested that the stereotype has an influence on those attracted to the profession with many new entrants underestimating the importance of communication skills and overestimating the importance of numeracy in the role</p>



<p>The&nbsp;Big Four auditors&nbsp;are the largest employers of accountants worldwide. However, most accountants are employed in commerce, industry, and the&nbsp;public sector.</p>



<p>A PA (sometimes referred to as LPA—Licensed Public Accountant) is licensed by the state to practice accountancy to the same extent as are CPAs, although in some states PAs are not permitted to perform audits or reviews (notably Iowa, Minnesota, Oregon, &amp; South Carolina). A PA&#8217;s ability to practice out of state is very limited due to most states having phased out the PA designation. While most states no longer accept new PA license applicants, four states still accept PA applicants for practice privileges within the state. As with the CPA, the requirements for receiving the PA license vary from state to state. Most states require a passage of either two or three (out of four) sections of the CPA exam or passage of the Comprehensive Examination for Accreditation in Accounting which is administered and graded by the Accreditation Council for Accountancy and Taxation (ACAT).</p>



<p>A certified internal auditor (CIA) is granted a certificate from the Institute of Internal Auditors (IIA), provided that the candidate has passed a four-part examination. One of the four parts is waived if the candidate has already passed the CPA Exam. A CIA typically provides services directly to an employer rather than to the public.</p>



<p>This romantic location was the perfect spot to celebrate their love and exchange their vows.</p>



<p>So without wasting any more time, let’s get on to it. First up: Let’s look at some of the most crucial aspects or features that are required in every travel company website.</p>



<p>Enabling Online Travel Booking and Reservations</p>



<p>Before you can win over any visitor or potential customer, you must make a great first impression as a company. Your story about WHY and HOW your company came into existence is one of the most important things you can communicate to your audience.</p>



<p>If your visitors like you as a company, they are more likely to purchase services from you. So, your company’s story is crucial to be communicated in the right way and in the most beautiful manner possible.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p><em>The needs of a small-time tour operator are a lot different from the needs of a large international travel agency itself.</em></p><p><strong>Steve Doe –&nbsp;</strong>Partner</p></blockquote>



<hr class="wp-block-separator"/>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="alignright"><img src="https://rishidemos.com/church-hill/wp-content/uploads/sites/19/2021/09/Mask-Group-29-1-300x300.png" alt="" class="wp-image-3259"/></figure></div>



<p>Eventually, you must also offer them attractive and competitive tour packages. You must be able to clearly communicate to your customers what your services are, how they are different from others compelling manner.</p>



<p>Of course, you would want your visitors to conveniently reach out to you and contact you. You would want to display all the crucial information about your company, including a map that would show your visitors where exactly they will find you.</p>



<h5 id="displaying-company-information">Displaying Company Information</h5>



<p>Here are the major fear of rejection symptoms identified by psychologists:</p>



<ul><li>It’s all the better if you can accept payments online so that you can close the sales then and there.</li><li>It is much easier and convenient for your customers as well, and you too increase your chance of generating leads.</li><li>To make sure that your travel company website is compatible with some kind of online payment mechanism.</li><li>These will be crucial and highly beneficial for you later in the process.</li></ul>



<h1 id="h1-reject-the-fulfilling-prophecy">H1: Reject the Fulfilling Prophecy</h1>



<p>This is my average total monthly spending from one year living in Seattle’s Capitol Hill, one year living in San Francisco’s Upper Haight, one year traveling to 20 countries, and one month at a hotel in Bali. It is much cheaper for me to travel. Since the majority of my costs are from trains and flights, it’s significantly cheaper if I stay in one place.</p>



<h2 id="h2-focus-on-how-you-want-to-be">H2:Focus On How You Want to Be</h2>



<p>This is my average total monthly spending from one year living in Seattle’s Capitol Hill, one year living in San Francisco’s Upper Haight, one year traveling to 20 countries, and one month at a hotel in Bali. It is much cheaper for me to travel. Since the majority of my costs are from trains and flights.</p>



<h3 id="h3-construct-a-narrative">H3: Construct a Narrative</h3>



<p>Instead of working during the daylight hours and pushing all my free time to the worst part of the day, I prefer to enjoy the days and work at night. I get out of bed faster when I’m excited to go out, and when I don’t have to commute there’s just more time in the day. I like to work 7 days a week with flexible hours so I can take a day off when I please or enjoy an empty movie theater at 2pm.</p>



<h4 id="h4-tap-into-your-imagination">H4: Tap Into Your Imagination</h4>



<p>I now have friends all over the world whose life experiences are very different than mine and bring fresh perspectives to my ideas. I’m learning about the real problems that affect the world on a global scale, which will make me.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Answering your questions about automating accounts.</title>
		<link>https://dianneligue.github.io/acadportfolio/answering-your-questions-about-automating-accounts/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[kbligue]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 04:32:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Enterprise]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://dianneligue.github.io/acadportfolio/answering-your-questions-about-automating-accounts/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In&#160;bookkeeping, an&#160;account&#160;refers to&#160;assets,&#160;liabilities,&#160;income,&#160;expenses, and&#160;equity, as represented by individual&#160;ledger&#160;pages, to which changes in value are chronologically recorded with&#160;debit and credit&#160;entries. These entries, referred to as postings, become part of a&#160;book of [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>In&nbsp;bookkeeping, an&nbsp;<strong>account</strong>&nbsp;refers to&nbsp;assets,&nbsp;liabilities,&nbsp;income,&nbsp;expenses, and&nbsp;equity, as represented by individual&nbsp;ledger&nbsp;pages, to which changes in value are chronologically recorded with&nbsp;debit and credit&nbsp;entries. These entries, referred to as postings, become part of a&nbsp;<em>book of final entry</em>&nbsp;or&nbsp;ledger. Examples of common </p>



<p>A&nbsp;chart of accounts&nbsp;provides a listing of all financial accounts used by particular business, organization, or government agency.</p>



<p>The system of recording, verifying, and reporting such information is called&nbsp;accounting. Practitioners of accounting are called&nbsp;accountants.</p>



<p>Emotional ceremony, and some delicious dessert options–we’re talking pie&nbsp;<em>and&nbsp;</em>cake. So keep scrolling to see how these two lovebirds let the good times roll.</p>



<p>Eventually, you must also offer them attractive and competitive tourpackages. You must be able to clearly communicate to your customers what your services are, how they are different from others compelling manner.</p>



<p>So without wasting any more time, let’s get on to it. First up: Let’s look at some of the most crucial aspects or features that are required in every travel company website.</p>



<p>Enabling Online Travel Booking and Reservations</p>



<p>Before you can win over any visitor or potential customer, you must make a great first impression as a company. Your story about WHY and HOW your company came into existence is one of the most important things you can communicate to your audience.</p>



<p>If your visitors like you as a company, they are more likely to purchase services from you. So, your company’s story is crucial to be communicated in the right way and in the most beautiful manner possible.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p><em>The needs of a small-time tour operator are a lot different from the needs of a large international travel agency itself.</em></p><p><strong>Steve Doe –&nbsp;</strong>Partner</p></blockquote>



<hr class="wp-block-separator"/>



<p>Eventually, you must also offer them attractive and competitive tour packages. You must be able to clearly communicate to your customers what your services are, how they are different from others compelling manner.</p>



<p>Of course, you would want your visitors to conveniently reach out to you and contact you. You would want to display all the crucial information about your company, including a map that would show your visitors where exactly they will find you.</p>



<h5 id="displaying-company-information">Displaying Company Information</h5>



<p>Here are the major fear of rejection symptoms identified by psychologists:</p>



<ul><li>It’s all the better if you can accept payments online so that you can close the sales then and there.</li><li>It is much easier and convenient for your customers as well, and you too increase your chance of generating leads.</li><li>To make sure that your travel company website is compatible with some kind of online payment mechanism.</li><li>These will be crucial and highly beneficial for you later in the process.</li></ul>



<h1 id="h1-reject-the-fulfilling-prophecy">H1: Reject the Fulfilling Prophecy</h1>



<p>This is my average total monthly spending from one year living in Seattle’s Capitol Hill, one year living in San Francisco’s Upper Haight, one year traveling to 20 countries, and one month at a hotel in Bali. It is much cheaper for me to travel. Since the majority of my costs are from trains and flights, it’s significantly cheaper if I stay in one place.</p>



<h2 id="h2-focus-on-how-you-want-to-be">H2:Focus On How You Want to Be</h2>



<p>This is my average total monthly spending from one year living in Seattle’s Capitol Hill, one year living in San Francisco’s Upper Haight, one year traveling to 20 countries, and one month at a hotel in Bali. It is much cheaper for me to travel. Since the majority of my costs are from trains and flights.</p>



<h3 id="h3-construct-a-narrative">H3: Construct a Narrative</h3>



<p>Instead of working during the daylight hours and pushing all my free time to the worst part of the day, I prefer to enjoy the days and work at night. I get out of bed faster when I’m excited to go out, and when I don’t have to commute there’s just more time in the day. I like to work 7 days a week with flexible hours so I can take a day off when I please or enjoy an empty movie theater at 2pm.</p>



<h4 id="h4-tap-into-your-imagination">H4: Tap Into Your Imagination</h4>



<p>I now have friends all over the world whose life experiences are very different than mine and bring fresh perspectives to my ideas. I’m learning about the real problems that affect the world on a global scale, which will make me.</p>



<h5 id="h5-embrace-not-knowing">H5: Embrace Not Knowing</h5>



<p>There’s a growing community of “digital nomads” who live a location independent lifestyle. We’re software developers, designers, writers, journalists, engineers, and all sorts of people who share a passion for the work we do.</p>



<h6 id="h6-remember-you-will-survive">H6: Remember You Will Survive</h6>



<p>Three years ago I was preparing to leave my job at Microsoft to move to San Francisco to start a startup. My friend asked me “but why do you need to be in San Francisco when you can work on a computer from anywhere?” His question made a lot of sense. As I thought about it more, I began to question my assumptions about a “normal life” which don’t make sense in our modern world.</p>



<h1 id="h1-heading-1">H1: Heading 1</h1>



<h2 id="h2-heading-2">H2: Heading 2</h2>



<h3 id="h3-heading-3">H3: Heading 3</h3>



<h4 id="h4-heading-4">H4: Heading 4</h4>



<h5 id="h5-heading-5">H5: Heading 5</h5>



<h6 id="h6-heading-6">H6: Heading 6</h6>



<p>Three years ago I was preparing to leave my job at Microsoft to move to San Francisco to start a startup. My friend asked me “but why do you need to be in San Francisco when you can work on a computer from anywhere?” His question made a lot of sense. As I thought about it more, I began to question my assumptions about a “normal life” which don’t make sense in our modern world.</p>



<h5 id="displaying-company-information">Displaying Company Information</h5>



<p>Here are the major fear of rejection symptoms identified by psychologists:</p>



<ul><li>It’s all the better if you can accept payments online so that you can close the sales then and there.</li><li>It is much easier and convenient for your customers as well, and you too increase your chance of generating leads.</li><li>To make sure that your travel company website is compatible with some kind of online payment mechanism.</li><li>These will be crucial and highly beneficial for you later in the process.</li></ul>



<p>Three years ago I was preparing to leave my job at Microsoft to move to San Francisco to start a startup. My friend asked me “but why do you need to be in San Francisco when you can work on a computer from anywhere?” His question made a lot of sense. As I thought about it more, I began to question my assumptions about a “normal life” which don’t make sense in our modern world.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table><thead><tr><th><strong>Name</strong></th><th>Position</th><th>Office</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td>Erica Romaguera</td><td>Coach</td><td>Audi</td></tr><tr><td>Caleigh Jerde</td><td>Lawyer</td><td>Pizza Hut</td></tr><tr><td>Lucas Schultz</td><td>Librarian</td><td>Burberry</td></tr><tr><td>Carole Marvin</td><td>Educator</td><td>Starbucks</td></tr><tr><td>Woodrow Nikolaus</td><td>Massage Therapist</td><td>Jack Daniel’s</td></tr></tbody></table></figure>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Four biggest challenges to small business growth.</title>
		<link>https://dianneligue.github.io/acadportfolio/four-biggest-challenges-to-small-business-growth/</link>
					<comments>https://dianneligue.github.io/acadportfolio/four-biggest-challenges-to-small-business-growth/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[kbligue]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 04:31:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Enterprise]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://dianneligue.github.io/acadportfolio/four-biggest-challenges-to-small-business-growth/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Business&#160;is the activity of making one&#8217;s living or making money by producing or buying and selling&#160;products&#160;(such as goods and services).Simply put, it is &#8220;any activity or enterprise entered into for [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Business&nbsp;is the activity of making one&#8217;s living or making money by producing or buying and selling&nbsp;products&nbsp;(such as goods and services).Simply put, it is &#8220;any activity or enterprise entered into for profit.</p>



<p>Having a&nbsp;business name&nbsp;does not separate the business entity from the owner, which means that the owner of the business is responsible and liable for debts incurred by the business. If the business acquires debts, the creditors can go after the owner&#8217;s personal possessions. A business structure does not allow for corporate tax rates. The proprietor is personally taxed on all income from the business.</p>



<p>The term is also often used colloquially (but not by lawyers or by public officials) to refer to a&nbsp;company. A company, on the other hand, is a separate legal entity and provides for&nbsp;limited liability, as well as&nbsp;corporate tax&nbsp;rates. A company structure is more complicated and expensive to set up, but offers more protection and benefits for the owner.</p>



<p>Forms of business ownership vary by&nbsp;<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jurisdiction">jurisdiction</a>, but several common entities exist:</p>



<ul><li><strong>Sole proprietorship:</strong>&nbsp;A&nbsp;sole proprietorship, also known as a sole trader, is owned by one person and operates for their benefit. The owner operates the business alone and may hire&nbsp;employees. A sole proprietor has unlimited&nbsp;liability&nbsp;for all obligations incurred by the business, whether from&nbsp;operating costs&nbsp;or&nbsp;judgments&nbsp;against the business. All&nbsp;assets&nbsp;of the business belong to a sole proprietor, including, for example, a computer infrastructure, any&nbsp;inventory,&nbsp;manufacturing&nbsp;equipment, or&nbsp;retail&nbsp;fixtures, as well as any&nbsp;real property&nbsp;owned by the sole proprietor.</li><li><strong>Partnership:</strong>&nbsp;A&nbsp;partnership&nbsp;is a business owned by two or more people. In most forms of partnerships, each partner has unlimited liability for the debts incurred by the business. The three most prevalent types of for-profit partnerships arepartnerships,&nbsp;limited partnerships, and&nbsp;limited liability partnerships.</li><li><strong>A&nbsp;company limited by shares:</strong>&nbsp;The most common form of the company used for business ventures. Specifically, a limited company is a &#8220;company in which the liability of each shareholder is limited to the amount individually invested&#8221; with corporations being &#8220;the most common example of a limited company.&nbsp;This type of company is common in&nbsp;England&nbsp;and many English-speaking countries. </li></ul>



<p>You’ve got your announcement in mind, and now it’s time to get it down in words to share with you…</p>



<p>So without wasting any more time, let’s get on to it. First up: Let’s look at some of the most crucial aspects or features that are required in every travel company website.</p>



<p>Enabling Online Travel Booking and Reservations</p>



<p>Before you can win over any visitor or potential customer, you must make a great first impression as a company. Your story about WHY and HOW your company came into existence is one of the most important things you can communicate to your audience.</p>



<p>If your visitors like you as a company, they are more likely to purchase services from you. So, your company’s story is crucial to be communicated in the right way and in the most beautiful manner possible.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p><em>The needs of a small-time tour operator are a lot different from the needs of a large international travel agency itself.</em></p><p><strong>Steve Doe –&nbsp;</strong>Partner</p></blockquote>



<hr class="wp-block-separator"/>



<p>Eventually, you must also offer them attractive and competitive tour packages. You must be able to clearly communicate to your customers what your services are, how they are different from others compelling manner.</p>



<p>Of course, you would want your visitors to conveniently reach out to you and contact you. You would want to display all the crucial information about your company, including a map that would show your visitors where exactly they will find you.</p>



<h5 id="displaying-company-information">Displaying Company Information</h5>



<p>Here are the major fear of rejection symptoms identified by psychologists:</p>



<ul><li>It’s all the better if you can accept payments online so that you can close the sales then and there.</li><li>It is much easier and convenient for your customers as well, and you too increase your chance of generating leads.</li><li>To make sure that your travel company website is compatible with some kind of online payment mechanism.</li><li>These will be crucial and highly beneficial for you later in the process.</li></ul>



<h1 id="h1-reject-the-fulfilling-prophecy">H1: Reject the Fulfilling Prophecy</h1>



<p>This is my average total monthly spending from one year living in Seattle’s Capitol Hill, one year living in San Francisco’s Upper Haight, one year traveling to 20 countries, and one month at a hotel in Bali. It is much cheaper for me to travel. Since the majority of my costs are from trains and flights, it’s significantly cheaper if I stay in one place.</p>



<h2 id="h2-focus-on-how-you-want-to-be">H2:Focus On How You Want to Be</h2>



<p>This is my average total monthly spending from one year living in Seattle’s Capitol Hill, one year living in San Francisco’s Upper Haight, one year traveling to 20 countries, and one month at a hotel in Bali. It is much cheaper for me to travel. Since the majority of my costs are from trains and flights.</p>



<h3 id="h3-construct-a-narrative">H3: Construct a Narrative</h3>



<p>Instead of working during the daylight hours and pushing all my free time to the worst part of the day, I prefer to enjoy the days and work at night. I get out of bed faster when I’m excited to go out, and when I don’t have to commute there’s just more time in the day. I like to work 7 days a week with flexible hours so I can take a day off when I please or enjoy an empty movie theater at 2pm.</p>



<h4 id="h4-tap-into-your-imagination">H4: Tap Into Your Imagination</h4>



<p>I now have friends all over the world whose life experiences are very different than mine and bring fresh perspectives to my ideas. I’m learning about the real problems that affect the world on a global scale, which will make me.</p>



<h5 id="h5-embrace-not-knowing">H5: Embrace Not Knowing</h5>



<p>There’s a growing community of “digital nomads” who live a location independent lifestyle. We’re software developers, designers, writers, journalists, engineers, and all sorts of people who share a passion for the work we do.</p>



<h6 id="h6-remember-you-will-survive">H6: Remember You Will Survive</h6>



<p>Three years ago I was preparing to leave my job at Microsoft to move to San Francisco to start a startup. My friend asked me “but why do you need to be in San Francisco when you can work on a computer from anywhere?” His question made a lot of sense. As I thought about it more, I began to question my assumptions about a “normal life” which don’t make sense in our modern world.</p>



<h1 id="h1-heading-1">H1: Heading 1</h1>



<h2 id="h2-heading-2">H2: Heading 2</h2>



<h3 id="h3-heading-3">H3: Heading 3</h3>



<h4 id="h4-heading-4">H4: Heading 4</h4>



<h5 id="h5-heading-5">H5: Heading 5</h5>



<h6 id="h6-heading-6">H6: Heading 6</h6>



<p>Three years ago I was preparing to leave my job at Microsoft to move to San Francisco to start a startup. My friend asked me “but why do you need to be in San Francisco when you can work on a computer from anywhere?” His question made a lot of sense. As I thought about it more, I began to question my assumptions about a “normal life” which don’t make sense in our modern world.</p>



<h5 id="displaying-company-information">Displaying Company Information</h5>



<p>Here are the major fear of rejection symptoms identified by psychologists:</p>



<ul><li>It’s all the better if you can accept payments online so that you can close the sales then and there.</li><li>It is much easier and convenient for your customers as well, and you too increase your chance of generating leads.</li><li>To make sure that your travel company website is compatible with some kind of online payment mechanism.</li><li>These will be crucial and highly beneficial for you later in the process.</li></ul>



<p>Three years ago I was preparing to leave my job at Microsoft to move to San Francisco to start a startup. My friend asked me “but why do you need to be in San Francisco when you can work on a computer from anywhere?” His question made a lot of sense. As I thought about it more, I began to question my assumptions about a “normal life” which don’t make sense in our modern world.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-table"><table><thead><tr><th><strong>Name</strong></th><th>Position</th><th>Office</th></tr></thead><tbody><tr><td>Erica Romaguera</td><td>Coach</td><td>Audi</td></tr><tr><td>Caleigh Jerde</td><td>Lawyer</td><td>Pizza Hut</td></tr><tr><td>Lucas Schultz</td><td>Librarian</td><td>Burberry</td></tr><tr><td>Carole Marvin</td><td>Educator</td><td>Starbucks</td></tr><tr><td>Woodrow Nikolaus</td><td>Massage Therapist</td><td>Jack Daniel’s</td></tr></tbody></table></figure>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://dianneligue.github.io/acadportfolio/four-biggest-challenges-to-small-business-growth/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Internets effect on tax planning : a case study on business</title>
		<link>https://dianneligue.github.io/acadportfolio/internets-effect-on-tax-planning-a-case-study/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[kbligue]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 04:29:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Organization]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://dianneligue.github.io/acadportfolio/internets-effect-on-tax-planning-a-case-study/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A&#160;tax&#160;is a compulsory financial charge or some other type of levy imposed on a taxpayer (an individual or&#160;legal entity) by a&#160;governmental&#160;organization in order to fund&#160;government spending&#160;and various&#160;public expenditures.&#160;A failure to [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A&nbsp;tax&nbsp;is a compulsory financial charge or some other type of levy imposed on a taxpayer (an individual or&nbsp;legal entity) by a&nbsp;governmental&nbsp;organization in order to fund&nbsp;government spending&nbsp;and various&nbsp;public expenditures.&nbsp;A failure to pay, along with evasion of or resistance to taxation, is punishable by&nbsp;law. Taxes consist of&nbsp;direct&nbsp;or&nbsp;indirect taxes&nbsp;and may be paid in money or as its labor equivalent.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Eventually, you must also offer them attractive and competitive tour packages. You must be able to clearly communicate to your customers what your services are, how they are different from others compelling manner.</p>



<p>Of course, you would want your visitors to conveniently reach out to you and contact you. You would want to display all the crucial information about your company, including a map that would show your visitors where exactly they will find you.</p>



<h5 id="displaying-company-information">Displaying Company Information</h5>



<p>Here is the major fear of rejection symptoms identified by psychologists:</p>



<ul><li>It’s all the better if you can accept payments online so that you can close the sales then and there.</li><li>It is much easier and convenient for your customers as well, and you too increase your chance of generating leads.</li><li>To make sure that your travel company website is compatible with some kind of online payment mechanism.</li><li>These will be crucial and highly beneficial for you later in the process.</li></ul>



<h1 id="h1-reject-the-fulfilling-prophecy">H1: Reject the Fulfilling Prophecy</h1>



<p>This is my average total monthly spending from one year living in Seattle’s Capitol Hill, one year living in San Francisco’s Upper Haight, one year traveling to 20 countries, and one month at a hotel in Bali. It is much cheaper for me to travel. Since the majority of my costs are from trains and flights, it’s significantly cheaper if I stay in one place.</p>



<h2 id="h2-focus-on-how-you-want-to-be">H2:Focus On How You Want to Be</h2>



<p>This is my average total monthly spending from one year living in Seattle’s Capitol Hill, one year living in San Francisco’s Upper Haight, one year traveling to 20 countries, and one month at a hotel in Bali. It is much cheaper for me to travel. Since the majority of my costs are from trains and flights.</p>



<h3 id="h3-construct-a-narrative">H3: Construct a Narrative</h3>



<p>Instead of working during the daylight hours and pushing all my free time to the worst part of the day, I prefer to enjoy the days and work at night. I get out of bed faster when I’m excited to go out, and when I don’t have to commute there’s just more time in the day. I like to work 7 days a week with flexible hours so I can take a day off when I please or enjoy an empty movie theater at 2 pm.</p>



<h4 id="h4-tap-into-your-imagination">H4: Tap Into Your Imagination</h4>



<p>I now have friends all over the world whose life experiences are very different than mine and bring fresh perspectives to my ideas. I’m learning about the real problems that affect the world on a global scale, which will make me.</p>



<h5 id="h5-embrace-not-knowing">H5: Embrace Not Knowing</h5>



<p>There’s a growing community of “digital nomads” who live a location-independent lifestyle. We’re software developers, designers, writers, journalists, engineers, and all sorts of people who share a passion for the work we do.</p>



<h6 id="h6-remember-you-will-survive">H6: Remember You Will Survive</h6>



<p>Three years ago I was preparing to leave my job at Microsoft to move to San Francisco to start a startup. My friend asked me “but why do you need to be in San Francisco when you can work on a computer from anywhere?” His question made a lot of sense. As I thought about it more, I began to question my assumptions about a “normal life” which don’t make sense in our modern world.</p>



<h1 id="h1-heading-1">H1: Heading 1</h1>



<h2 id="h2-heading-2">H2: Heading 2</h2>



<h3 id="h3-heading-3">H3: Heading 3</h3>



<h4 id="h4-heading-4">H4: Heading 4</h4>



<h5 id="h5-heading-5">H5: Heading 5</h5>



<h6 id="h6-heading-6">H6: Heading 6</h6>



<p>Three years ago I was preparing to leave my job at Microsoft to move to San Francisco to start a startup. My friend asked me “but why do you need to be in San Francisco when you can work on a computer from anywhere?” His question made a lot of sense. As I thought about it more, I began to question my assumptions about a “normal life” which don’t make sense in our modern world.</p>



<h5 id="displaying-company-information">Displaying Company Information</h5>



<p>Here are the major fear of rejection symptoms identified by psychologists:</p>



<ul><li>It’s all the better if you can accept payments online so that you can close the sales then and there.</li><li>It is much easier and convenient for your customers as well, and you too increase your chance of generating leads.</li><li>To make sure that your travel company website is compatible with some kind of online payment mechanism.</li><li>These will be crucial and highly beneficial for you later in the process.</li></ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
